TUYET LE

• London, UK | ■ tuyet.a.le@hotmail.co.uk | in linkedin.com/in/toowee | • github.com/toowee-le | □ toowee.dev

SUMMARY

Charity worker turned front-end web developer after discovering a passion for web development. Currently transitioning via the self-taught route gaining experience building projects with HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript and Node. Regular attendee at codebar and Code First Girl alumni.

SKILLS

Programming HTML · CSS · Sass · Bootstrap

JavaScript ES6+ · Node.js · Express

Tools Webpack · Git/Github · TDD · Heroku

Visual Studio Code · WordPress

Design Illustrator · InDesign · XD

Other Project Management · Research

EDUCATION & COURSES

Udacity Front End Web Developer Nanodegree (Online)

Mar 2020 - current

Built 5 projects with HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript,
Node.js/Express, Webpack, Service Workers and APIs

FreeCodeCamp (Online)

Oct 2019 - current

- Currently completing the React certification
- Completed <u>Responsive Web Design</u> and <u>JavaScript</u> <u>Algorithms & Data Structures</u> certifications

Code First Girls & Goldman Sachs - Python Programming *Feb - Apr 2020*

- Pair programming with 3 other team members to learn Python using PyCharm
- Built a cocktail recipe finder back-end app with Python and a public API for final course project

Code First Girls - Introduction to Web Development *Oct 2019 - Dec 2019*

 Worked in a team to build a cat adoption website built with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and jQuery. Awarded runner-up prize for best website (Link to Github)

Brunel University - BSc Psychology and Sociology

Sept 2011 - July 2014

First Class Honours awarded

PROJECTS

Natural Language Processing | <u>Live Project</u> | <u>Github</u>

A single-page Node-Express-Webpack web tool that analyses news articles using a text analysis API to interpret the author's emotions.

Portfolio | Live Project | Github

My personal website built with HTML, CSS/SCSS and JavaScript which showcases self-initiated projects.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Charity Administration & Finance Officer

Saving Faces, - London, Mar 2017 - present

- Maintain all websites and develop web pages using semantic markup and CSS built on WordPress
- Initiated and managed the roll out of WordPress to resolve hacking issues with legacy CMS and improve front-end efficiency resulting in 10% increase in monthly traffic across all sites
- Improve charity's branding by redesigning fundraising materials for emails and print publication
- Lead social media and strategic communication meetings with research team/CEO to promote studies reaching 5000+ readers globally
- Implement Trello to streamline multiple projects and set goals improving office collaboration of 8 people
- Directly support the CEO and Trustees in the governance of the charity and chiefly manage the admin and finance department of 3 people

Honorary Clinical Researcher

Saving Faces - London, Jan 2016 - Mar 2017

- Assisted clinicians and statisticians in managing 3 major facial surgery clinical trials and audits
- Provided operational telephone support to 50+ hospitals for a new major NHS national audit
- Designed surveys with HTML to gather patient and public feedback on new clinical trials

Lead Administrator

Chobham Academy - London, Oct 2014 - Jan 2016

- Led parent outreach by launching and designing the weekly print newsletter improving parental engagement, communication and events attendance
- Maintained the primary school's CRM